https://statevacuum.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode/

Menu
MieleMiele VacuumsCordless VacuumsMiele Homecare VacuumsCanister VacuumsUpright VacuumsStick VacuumsRobot VacuumsBagless VacuumsMiele Bags and FiltersBag& Filter PacksBagsFiltersMiele AccessoriesFloor ToolsHand ToolsAccessory KitsWandsPower Nozzles & Turbo BrushesMiele Hoses Miele Coffee MakersCounter Top Coffee MakersBuilt-In Coffee MakersMiele Care ProductsDishwasher CareLaundry CareCooking CareCoffee CareMiele Fashion MasterMiele AppliancesCooktopsDishwashersDryersOvensRangesRefrigerationRotary IronsVentilationWarming DrawersWashersSeboSebo CanistersSebo UprightsSebo Carpet CleanersSebo BagsSebo FiltersAirbelt EVacuums & Floor CareVacuum CleanersBrandsMieleSeboRiccarDysonDust CareFuller BrushHooverLindhausNacecarePowrflitePro-teamRoyalSanitaireSonicleanCordless VacuumsCanister VacuumsUpright VacuumsStick/Broom VacuumsHandheld VacuumsRobot VacuumsBackpack VacuumsWet/Dry VacuumsIndustrial VacuumsWide Area VacuumsVacuum Bags, Filters, Belts and PartsVacuum BagsVacuum FiltersVacuum BeltsVacuum PartsVacuum Tools & AttachmentsAttachmentsPower NozzlesHosesAttachment KitsCarpet and Floor CleanersBare Floor CleanersCarpet CleanersCleaning ProductsWindow CleaningMops & BucketsMicrofiber TowelsVacuum BumpersSweepersAllergy & Air CareAir PurifiersAir Purifier UnitsAir FiltersAllergy ChemicalsBedding & EncasementsChemical Free CleaningHEPA VacuumsHEPA VacuumsHEPA Vacuum BagsHEPA Vacuum FiltersFansCommercial EquipmentAuto ScrubbersExtractorsFloor MachinesHigh Speed Flooor MachinesCommercial VacuumsUpright VacuumsCanister VacuumsCordless VacuumsRestaurant VacuumsEPA Approved HEPABackpack VacuumsWet/Dry VacuumsJanitorial SuppliesMicrofiberWindow CleaningDustersJanitorial CartsMops & BucketsGrout and TileBackpack VacuumsWet/Dry VacuumsClothing CareClothes SteamersIroningIroning BoardsRotary IronsSteam IronsCentral VacuumsDo It Yourself Rough-in KitsInstallation MaterialsInlet ValvesStandard InletsElectric InletsToe KicksFittingsPipeComplete SystemsHide a Hose Central Vacuum SystemsHide A HoseAttachmentsFittingsHandlesHosesInlets & Toe KicksVacuum UnitsVacuum UnitsAttachment KitsAttachments and ToolsPower NozzlesHosesBagsFiltersIntercomsResidentialVoice OnlyVoice & MusicVoice, Music, & VideoCommercialPartition IntercomsBrandsAiphoneHavenIntrasonicIntrasonic IntercomsIntrasonic SpeakersIntrasonic Music SystemsM&S IntercomsValetSelective Call IntercomMaster StationsVideo IntercomRemote StationsWhole Home IntercomSpeakersReplace Nutone IntercomReplace Nutone IM-203Replace Nutone IM-303Replace Nutone IM-313Replace Nutone IM-406Replace Nutone SM428Replace Nutone IM 806Replace Nutone IM-2003Replace Nutone 2011/2012Replace Nutone 2015/2016Replace Nutone 2031/2032Replace Nutone 2053/2054Replace Nutone 2055/2056Replace Nutone 2057/2058Replace Nutone 2063/2064Replace Nutone 2067/2068Replace Nutone 2071Replace Nutone 2090/2091Replace Nutone 2401/2402Replace Nutone 2540/2541Replace Nutone 2542Replace Nutone 2561/2562Replace Nutone IM-3003Replace Nutone IM-3103Replace Nutone IMA-3303Replace Nutone IM-4006Replace Nutone IMA-4406Replace Nutone IM5006New Installation IntercomsPartition Intercoms (e.g. Ticket Booths)About UsMaison BergerLampsFragrancesVirus ReliefClorox Total 360
Account
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Just like you we dislike getting unwanted calls and email from people who sell our information. We will never give your information away to ANYONE. Email addresses voluntarily given to us will be used for our own electronic marketing purposes, but we will only market to you if you check the box to recieve marketing emails. If you accidentally subscribe or would like to unsubscribe for any reason you will be given the opportunity in each email.
This privacy policy sets out how State Vacuum uses and protects any information that you give State Vacuum when you use this website. State Vacuum is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. State Vacuum may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
If and only if YOu authorize us to send your promotional emails, we may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. YOUR INFORMATION WILL NEVER BE GIVEN OR SOLD TO ANYONE ELSE
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at sales@statevacuum.com
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to .
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
List of cookies we collect
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
COOKIE nameCOOKIE Description
CART
The association with your shopping cart.
CATEGORY_INFO
Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.
COMPARE
The items that you have in the Compare Products list.
CURRENCY
Your preferred currency
CUSTOMER
An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.
CUSTOMER_AUTH
An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.
CUSTOMER_INFO
An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS
Stores the Customer Segment ID
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE
A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.
FRONTEND
You sesssion ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to edit their orders.
LAST_CATEGORY
The last category you visited.
LAST_PRODUCT
The most recent product you have viewed.
NEWMESSAGE
Indicates whether a new message has been received.
NO_CACHE
Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.
POLL
The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.
POLLN
Information on what polls you have voted on.
RECENTLYCOMPARED
The items that you have recently compared.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS
The products that you have recently viewed.
WISHLIST
An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.
WISHLIST_CNT
The number of items in your Wishlist.
2017 State Vacuum. All Rights Reserved.
